[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This medical term refers to a condition, characterized by enlargement of the thyroid gland.", "correct_answer": "Goiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Sore throat", "Mumps", "Boils"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular singer appeared in the 2003 action movie Once Upon a Time in Mexico?", "correct_answer": "Enrique Iglesias", "incorrect_answers": ["Shakira", "Christina Aguilera", "Ricky Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This statesman, born in Houghton Hall, Norfolk in 1676, is generally regarded as the first Prime Minister of Great Britain.", "correct_answer": "Robert Walpole", "incorrect_answers": ["David Gladstone", "Henry Cavendish", "Benjamin Disraeli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nautilus is the closest living relative of the ammonite.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The German word edelweiss, referring to one of the most famous European mountain flowers, means what in English?", "correct_answer": "Noble and white", "incorrect_answers": ["Frost and noble", "Beautiful and white", "Frost and white"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1952, this disease struck the U.S. and became the worst epidemic in the nations history at that time.", "correct_answer": "Polio", "incorrect_answers": ["Small Pox", "Malaria", "Whooping Cough"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which elephant subspecies is the largest on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Savanna Elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["Sri Lankan Elephant", "Indian Elephant", "Forest Elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What company is generally regarded as the largest toy distributor in the world?", "correct_answer": "McDonalds", "incorrect_answers": ["Mattel", "Barbie", "Fisher Price"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Bandits real name is never mentioned in the movie Smokey and the Bandit.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What organization was started by Carrie Chapman Catt?", "correct_answer": "League of Women Voters", "incorrect_answers": ["National Universal Suffrage League", "Democratic National Committee", "The Right to Life Party"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Solve for X:\n\nX = [(number of arms on a squid) - (height in feet of an NBA basketball hoop)] * [number of minutes taken for light from the sun to reach the earth]", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["8", "24", "72"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is generally considered to be the second longest symphony?", "correct_answer": "Shostakovitchs Leningrad Symphony", "incorrect_answers": ["Mozarts Jupiter Symphony", "Mahlers Symphony No. 3 in D minor", "Beethovens Symphony Number 9 (the Choral)"]}]